( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
=No Doubt In Us=
(Adapted from the Manman comic No Doubt in Us)
=Episode 11=
You told me to say that to Mother today.
You knew Prince Ning
and the Marquis of Zhenbei
would cause trouble.
Their plans for the autumn hunt
and the Yin Yang dolls failed.
Now, Jinming is unfit for the burden.
They think I'm only good for fighting.
So they won't let go of
this once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
You should wear this soft armor instead.
They might not kill me directly.
The battlefield is dangerous.
I'll feel more at ease if you wear it.
You wear it.
Come.
I have something to give you.
What is it? So mysterious.
We've never been apart
since you entered the palace.
You're going to the border
to fight for me.
I guess you'll miss me.
Put it on.
On the battlefield, it will be
as if I'm with you at all times.
Xiao Jinyun.
Look.
Don't you look handsome in this armor?
I really wish I could wear the armor
and take the risk for you.
Becoming you
gives me the chance
to become the one I want to be.
Ever since I was young, I've wanted
to charge into battle
and serve the nation
like my father and brothers.
That has been my dream since childhood.
This is not an adventure.
It's the best gift
Your Majesty has given me.
I'm not worried about you.
I'm worried that my body
will hold you back.
Have you forgotten? I have another name.
Father has summoned General Xu's family
to the palace for a meal again.
So noisy!
You're right.
Who's there?
Sorry, I missed.
Trying to assassinate us?
I was trying to hit birds.
Their droppings
were almost on your heads.
Who are you?
Why are you here?
I came to the palace with my father.
But I got lost.
My name is Xu Tie.
I'm the third son of the Xu family.
Easy.
You can play with this.
What about you? Will you remember me?
I am...
- Xu Tie.
How about this?
I'll take Your Majesty
to test out your body.
♪Parting clouds
to pluck the waxing moon♪
Your Majesty.
How long are you going
to keep holding me?
♪Chill flame, window shade,
console my grieving soul♪
I thought you were going
to do something with my body.
Why did you bring me
to such a high place?
I want you to see
if I can charge forward
and fight the enemy.
Be careful!
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
Come.
I'll hold your hand.
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪
When I was little,
my father and eldest brother
often went to battle,
leaving me home alone.
I would run to the roof
to look at the sky.
Because I knew
I was under the same sky as them.
And we might be
looking at the same star.
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
Xiao Jinyun.
I promise.
I will return safely.
I keep my word.
Xu Yu.
So will I.
No doubt in us.
I keep my word.
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
Look, stars.
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪All who believed love would never fade♪
The army is assembled.
Waiting for Your Majesty's word.
♪Like a song, like a dream, like a play♪
♪This life is but a solitary boat♪
♪No one ferries me
across this sea of pain♪
♪Fate tears us apart♪
♪Embrace again, hurt again, start again♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
Wait for me to return.
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
I'll wait for you.
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪
Set out!
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪All who believed love would never fade♪
♪The wind scatters countless sorrows♪
♪Like a song, like a dream, like a play♪
♪This life is but a solitary boat♪
♪No one ferries me
across this sea of pain♪
Stop.
Your Majesty, what's wrong?
Why do I feel there's an ambush?
Ambush?
Father!
Xu Han is here!
(Xu Han)
Everyone!
Kill them!
- Kill!
(Counter thrust?)
(Fengyi Palace)
So this is your review work?
Do it again.
Or else, no dinner for you.
No, please!
I've done it five times.
Could you bear to see me starve?
Your Highness.
The Empress and Prince Xiaoyao
are alone in the garden.
What?
They're arm-in-arm, so intimate!
It's barely been days
since His Majesty departed for war.
And now, they are intimate.
The Empress's position
will finally be mine.
Congratulations in advance.
You are rewarded.
Thank you.
Today, luckily, you arrived in time.
It was close, but we're safe.
But Marshal Xu,
how did you know
about the ambush in the valley?
Sit and explain.
Your Majesty,
I observed that Dada appeared quiet,
but small squads
had been dispatched each night.
When imperial reports
confirmed Your Majesty's expedition,
I deduced that they would
ambush you in the valley.
(My father is always the smartest.)
Marshal Xu,
you're a battle-hardened general.
You know the military inside out.
You flatter me, Your Majesty.
Report!
Your Majesty,
we captured a man
among the fleeing enemies.
Bring him.
Yes.
Bring him!
Who are you?
I...
I'm a refugee.
Those soldiers captured me
to force me into hard labor.
Refugees never fled
to deserted wastelands.
Your Majesty, I can tell he's a spy.
I'm not a spy!
You saved me.
Let me stay with you.
We're heading to war.
Why bring dead weight like you?
I know some martial arts.
I can aid you in battle.
Your Majesty.
Let's have a sparring match.
Don't!
Release him.
(Our family's sword technique!)
(Yu only entered the palace a year ago.)
(With the Emperor's physique,)
(how is he so proficient
with this technique?)
(And that counter thrust
earlier was clearly...)
Just as I thought.
You're a woman!
♪Parting clouds
to pluck the waxing moon♪
♪Brewing a pot of bygone years♪
♪Chill flame, window shade,
console my grieving soul♪
♪Drunk through lifetimes
with no dreams returned♪
♪If not for letting go, how could I
bear to shatter this dream♪
♪Returning to drift
through the mortal world♪
♪Like her, like me, like you♪
♪Hairpins carved
with endless sighs and regrets♪
♪Fate laid bare my deepest thoughts♪
♪Like vows, like remorse, like love♪
♪Loving, hurting,
and regretting our late meeting♪
♪Tell me, after all this entanglement,
who regrets it more♪